This is how I'll become.
Supreme Commander!
A hero!
This is my story!
The dark in the dark,
The one and the one, The one and
the one, The tears of sadness?
And the fear of the dream! Oh, oh, oh,
oh,
oh.
I've seen a dream.
It's not as high as I can.
I got a chance to the number of people.
What did you find?
I was connected to you.
I'll never end, but I'll never end!
I'll never end, you'll never end!
I will never end this world.
I'll never end this world!
I'll never end it. I'll never end it?
Miss Shushu. Miss Himari.
Commander. Mr. Yuki.
Please let them come back.
All of them safe and soundly.
Damn, I can't get free!
Now let's get this party started!
I feel surprisingly calm.
After putting my team in danger,
I needed time to cool off.
My heart is on fire, but I
can fight with a level head.
Without Yuki, I've got less
firepower at my disposal.
So that means... No!
For each and every person that you've
murdered, I'll slice you to pieces!
Not so!
Teleportation isn't the only
trick up her sleeve! Okay.
Superhuman speed.
I can't pinpoint her position.
That's my sister-in-law.
I'll go for a wider range!
Damn!
I missed her!
Ame na mitari!
That's an awful lot of damage.
I thought you and your friends lived here.
We're ditching this place!
They've already evacuated the area.
Over consuming peaches is dangerous.
They've been my source of
energy since the accident.
I'll
beat your ass.
Especially if you're a disgusting
bitch preying on my brother!
Big sis weapons in her arsenal.
A resilient physical form and
a blast attack from her mouth.
She can harden and manipulate her hair
and gain strength by consuming peaches.
Pretty?
That's pretty impressive.
But help!
When I eat peaches, it
heightens my senses too!
She's too fast for me to attack.
All you can do is flee.
So I'll wear you down, then take you out.
So it's a war of attrition. She wants.
Unfortunately for her, as the commander,
I can teleport 666 times in a row.
Comes with the territory.
Guess I'm...
Holding out until Kyo wins.
The moment I get a chance, I'll strike.
Hitting or grabbing me won't
work when my body is slippery.
OK, then, without further delay!
Wa-bam!
Are you okay?
I am.
It really stings, but I'll be fine.
Sorry, but hitting me with a little
boulder isn't gonna do you much good.
Coco juice.
Thanks to the peaches, my stamina and
my regenerative abilities got enhanced.
And Kuma's even tougher than I am!
There's not a single scratch on her!
I just wanna get away and save Yuki!
You talking about Yuki, Wakura?
Yeah, that's right!
The guy you kidnapped!
He better be safe!
Don't worry about him,
I licked him all better.
Licked him?
Our boss has a soft spot for
him too. Soft spot? Come here.
Yuki Wakura belongs to
us now, so give it up!
Their next targets are your commanders.
Then the Onmyou Bureau.
We're gonna raise all kinds of hell
so the whole country knows we exist.
That massive Shuki.
It's been documented by
the defense force before.
It was spotted in a mishap
in Kagoshima eight years ago.
All threats to innocent lives end here.
Now that's more like it.
Remember what we discussed.
Let's go with Formation S.
Are you sure? Huh?
We'll use Formation S to wipe the floor
with you pathetic pipsqueaks! Excuse me!
Bring it on! Let's go!
Hey, does the S stand for see you later?
There she is!
We're really doing this?
Polarize her, Kuma!
Here goes!
Don't forget, I can shrink myself too!
The S in formation S stands for small!
And now, we grow!
Gah!
Paradigm Shaft!
Crazy, she won!
Idiot!
That attack won't work on...
Oh, Zeus!
Crap, this isn't good!
You should never piss off a girl in love.
Which means you were
doomed from the start.
Or Shuki?
I might be in trouble.
Huh?
Hang on, Sahara!
Ah!
Ah! Ah! Golden hour!
Rewind five seconds!
Himari!
More Shuki are hiding in the back! What?
Sneaking in from the hive? Cowards!
How did she know that?
My Hitori Shizuka lets me slip past humans
unnoticed, including the Onmio Bureau.
That little nuisance.
Where did that humanoid Shuki go?
Golden hour!
Free for five seconds!
Damn it, they're targeting Himari.
Yachi-ho, what just?
Shut the hell up.
Listen to me, you need to stay
behind me so I can protect you.
Golden hour, freeze for five seconds.
I've already used my ability
too many times in a row.
The humanoid, where is she?
Got you!
I'll grant you a beautiful death!
I know you've been protecting me.
It's written all over your face.
But now it's my turn.
A little sister can
protect her big sister too!
She disappeared into the ground!
This isn't effective enough.
I'll have to lure out the enemy first.
Hold on a second.
My ability's ready to go.
You need to stick close.
Don't you fret, Akura.
We'll capitalize on their weaknesses.
Victory will be ours it's too big of a
distance get closer to me like this now.
This is an Azuma battle
formation it's the ultimate
defense if they launch an
attack while I'm moving
there's a small chance
they'll overpower me before I
strike a pose but if I wait
in this position I should
be able to react get cozy
come on this isn't the
time to be shy no what's
the matter the enemy could
decide to ignore us and we
can't let her head for the
commanders we have to move
okay look there's a limit
to how many times I can
use my ability we have to
be precise I have a plan
a secret weapon I've been
saving for the right moment
secret weapon it'd be my
first time using it in
combat but if it works it'll
lure her out of hiding the
question is are you sure
you can actually pull
something like that off I'm not
the same person as I was
back then after joining the
seventh squad and fighting
in the exhibition match.
I've become a lot stronger.
Please trust me on this. I can do it.
If you're that determined, then go ahead.
I'll never hit the enemy
if I'm shooting blindly.
But...
What if I shoot blindly in all directions?
Full burst fire!
There she is!
Are you trying to kill yourself?
This is suicide!
That's not gonna happen!
Crime time!
Rewind for ten seconds!
The plan worked out.
You did an excellent job.
Above us, to the right,
45 degrees! Right! Fire!
Not bad, little sister.
I'll return the favor when we get back.
I'm still not going back
home with you, but thanks.
I have got to find Aoba.
A little space between
Kyo and the Unihorn.
Exactly what I've been waiting for.
She tricked me?
He threw up her rhythm. Thank you.
I'm not letting you target me!
I know your mood's inside and out
Ame no mitori!
No!
Tidka, no!
Her blast attack got faster too.
Oops, looks like I
nicked you with my beam.
Why didn't you attack me when
you had the opportunity to?
If I'd finished you off, it would
have made Yuki really upset.
Even I was shocked that I
couldn't go through with it.
Careless mistake It's
strange I've been having all
sorts of new feelings I can
take care of myself You don't
need to worry about my life
But I love that you took
Yuki's feelings into consideration
I'm starting to like you
I see it
Our bright future With my sister-in-law
big sister drop the sister
already are you okay
fighting might be difficult
if you flee now i'd be willing to
look away but we have not changed
our mind about storming the we
will not retreat
they
killed
Akura
and they followed us to the tunnels
it seems as
though your friends
are running on empty so let me
ask you this do you You surrender.
You wish.
What was that?
Over here, say hello to the gods.
It was easy to find you on account
of that huge ruckus you made.
Coco, no! Hold on!
They've got great vitality.
I'm thinking maybe we should bring
the two of them with us, just in case.
Wait a minute!
I thought they were your friends!
Please don't start lumping us in
with these inferior mutts! Behold!
The eight Thunder Gods stand before you!
We are the almighty leaders of the Shuki!
They control the Shuki?
The eight Thunder Gods?
That's right.
It is our duty to destroy the human race.
We're divine beings.
Feel free to worship us.
Jouryuu?
I don't care what you are, I am...
A big sister!
Ah!
Kitomaru?
What are you doing?
Oh, that?
That Shuki has been bitten
by one of my snakes,
thereby restoring to its
original murderous nature.
Go on, no need for you to hold back.
Do all the damage you want.
Keep your hands off my sister!
It's time.
Let's go.
Together we will force
them to bow down! Right!
Prepare to die!
But it's a simple thing to do.
It starts with you.
It's a special time.
The energy and the body of your body.
It's what you're telling me.
It's the first time. It's the second time.
It's the second time.
I need to shake your power.
I'm going to be together with two hands.
I'm going to keep coming.
I'm going to keep you
back, I'm going to be hard.
I'm going to be on a train.
I'm going to leave you.
Okay, believe it or not, I got my
hands on Miss Alba's list of secrets.
It's called Invincible, which means
she can grow her hair out well.
It's very long and powerful,
and it's strong enough to strangle
a large-sized Shuki to death.
Oh, how creepy.
Eating peaches to boost one's
energy can be very risky.
Miss Alba's the only
one who can handle it.
That's Yuki's sister.
This will be the last of my series, but
I look forward to seeing you again soon.
Goodbye!